[{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678878577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":25850,"timeElapsed":72751},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678889482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":10903,"timeElapsed":83657},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678896592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":7108,"timeElapsed":90767},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678900567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3973,"timeElapsed":94742},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678905535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4967,"timeElapsed":99710},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678910128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4592,"timeElapsed":104303},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678914341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4212,"timeElapsed":108516},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678920351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":6008,"timeElapsed":114526},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678925074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4722,"timeElapsed":119249},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678942373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":15758,"timeElapsed":136548},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678947329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4954,"timeElapsed":141504},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678951663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4333,"timeElapsed":145838},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678954434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2769,"timeElapsed":148609},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678958793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4358,"timeElapsed":152968},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678961047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2251,"timeElapsed":155222},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678963653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2604,"timeElapsed":157828},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678966826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3171,"timeElapsed":161001},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678969226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2398,"timeElapsed":163401},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678981976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":11237,"timeElapsed":176151},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678985206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3228,"timeElapsed":179381},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678991224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":6017,"timeElapsed":185399},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678993382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2156,"timeElapsed":187556},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678997216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3832,"timeElapsed":191390},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678999201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1984,"timeElapsed":193376},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679004003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4800,"timeElapsed":198178},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679006826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2821,"timeElapsed":201001},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679008959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2131,"timeElapsed":203134},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679017575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7531,"timeElapsed":211750},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679019658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2082,"timeElapsed":213833},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679022672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3012,"timeElapsed":216847},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679025143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2468,"timeElapsed":219317},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679029007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3863,"timeElapsed":223182},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679031216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2208,"timeElapsed":225391},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679033450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2232,"timeElapsed":227625},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679038249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4797,"timeElapsed":232424},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679040231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":1981,"timeElapsed":234406},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679050500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":9039,"timeElapsed":244675},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679052636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":2134,"timeElapsed":246811},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679055318,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2680,"timeElapsed":249493},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679057672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2353,"timeElapsed":251847},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679060026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2352,"timeElapsed":254201},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679062672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2644,"timeElapsed":256847},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679065134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2460,"timeElapsed":259309},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679067964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2829,"timeElapsed":262139},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679070497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":2532,"timeElapsed":264672},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679076599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5086,"timeElapsed":270774},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679079481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2881,"timeElapsed":273655},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679081898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2416,"timeElapsed":276073},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679083771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1871,"timeElapsed":277946},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679091422,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7648,"timeElapsed":285596},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679095560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4136,"timeElapsed":289734},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679097916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2354,"timeElapsed":292090},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679100260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2343,"timeElapsed":294435},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679102280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2018,"timeElapsed":296455},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679103858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1576,"timeElapsed":298033},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679131608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":26672,"timeElapsed":325783},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679134127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2518,"timeElapsed":328302},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679137661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":3532,"timeElapsed":331836},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679139590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1928,"timeElapsed":333765},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679142134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2542,"timeElapsed":336309},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679144638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2503,"timeElapsed":338813},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679149253,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4613,"timeElapsed":343428},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679152229,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2974,"timeElapsed":346403},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679154637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2406,"timeElapsed":348811},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679156377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1739,"timeElapsed":350552},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679163702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":6283,"timeElapsed":357876},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679165378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1676,"timeElapsed":359553},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679167465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2086,"timeElapsed":361640},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679170211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2745,"timeElapsed":364386},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679172929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2717,"timeElapsed":367104},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679174797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1866,"timeElapsed":368972},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679177451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2653,"timeElapsed":371626},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679180333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2880,"timeElapsed":374508},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679182011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1676,"timeElapsed":376185},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679186431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":3255,"timeElapsed":380606},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679189041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":2609,"timeElapsed":383216},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679191701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2659,"timeElapsed":385876},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679193803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2102,"timeElapsed":387978},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679196901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3096,"timeElapsed":391076},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679199098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2196,"timeElapsed":393273},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679201480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2380,"timeElapsed":395655},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679204328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":2846,"timeElapsed":398503},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679205823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":1493,"timeElapsed":399998},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679212891,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5995,"timeElapsed":407066},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679214718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1826,"timeElapsed":408893},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679217180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2460,"timeElapsed":411355},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679219000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1818,"timeElapsed":413175},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679221274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2272,"timeElapsed":415449},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679223769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2494,"timeElapsed":417944},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679225978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2208,"timeElapsed":420153},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679228081,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2101,"timeElapsed":422256},{"subjectID":"h87o7lj2w6","prolificID":"662d57d09714cf1c25756326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d1812df5793486bd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679230057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1974,"timeElapsed":424231}]